Hello, Learn German in Hindi,
welcome to this episode. From today, in the
next episode, we are going to learn to
make complex sentences and complex structures. So,
you start
with a simpler concept. That is, there are
10,000 points, base is a conjunction. This is a
conjunction, it is basically an adverb. So, let
us see how to use it. Basically, it would be '
dit almond' or 'phir' in Hindi.
Therefore, and 'trodden' would be 'amle'
in Hindi. Still, still, how to use it, let
us see. It is a very simple
usage. We have to join 2 seconds. We
need a little change. First of all, we will say simple. I
like tea, that is why I drink tea. I
like teammates for writing. This is simple. So, what will be the
first sentence?
What will be the second sentence? This trick will make
fast pairs. So, this will
come only in the country India and
I will give you some simple thing in keeping that
it will be the lesson of 10 years and second sentence.
10 years and second sentence.  If it becomes a part of the sentence
then if it becomes a part of the second sentence then if it has got
10 years on the first question then the
second should be declared that is why
this mask tehsil Priyanka Ishte very
simple this hitting 10 years printer instant
and accident make because India has
Sunday today so I do not work
that today this Sunday I will send a dash for the
door to work so what will happen such joint after all
this updater next add what will happen 10
years ago will come second puja karvai ga add don't
Id at the place butter this kunth very simple
edit now the opposite of this is if I have to tell you
that I like it a lot still
I would like to
come live coffee not dharai siding team then the
rest of the structure will remain the same this trick
of this route will spread this trick cut to add a
bit so what will happen this mask coffee
router drink is simple like the
rest still I work Sunday
still I work instant article
wash phone number what will happen this
Sunday a point is about  It will come in
truck stand testis joint walnut saver
batter it is very simple ride no meaning is
hard like that so what is the difference that the
dog thal and trodden which was
made a part of it in the composite second sentence that is why what has happened to the
worst position so
today I have deliberately learnt this
but next when the next concept which is
very important considered while
travelling in context to the colour which has become the
liner side and results in it
you are going to use it a lot if you have
understood all this then if they
have all the rest of them are absolutely normal such and there are a few
connectors best wagner lo whose
meaning is almost like huge or
john st johns meaning otherwise if you will not
come on time then I will go 12.1 is
not much use
for you just see this you have
understood only career 10 years and tiffin so
body no further a small thing some people
looking at the camera in the middle of strong global stance
you can also write small this year  Or you
can start the next sentence by making it difficult after seeing the above meaning, that is
Dharamjaigarh, okay good problem, it is fine, so you have come that
everyone must have understood this conserve, see you
in the next lesson with a little more
contact, thank you.